In this video, we're going to go through how you can
在本次视频中  我们来看一下
post your work for others to see on GitHub.
如何在 Github 上面发布你的项目
In this first part, you can see that in my repositories,
在我的代码仓库里 你可以看到
I have a Stack Overflow project
我有一个叫 Stack Overflow 的项目
related to the information we worked through in the previous lesson.
里面包含了一些我们之前课程里的课程资料
In order to post my work as you see here,
为了把项目放在这里
I went through a few steps that you're going to work through with me in this video.
需要完成几个步骤 我们现在一起来看一下
If we go back to the repositories page,
如果你回到之前代码仓库的这个页面
you'll see that there's a button here called New.
你会这里看到一个叫 New 的按钮
By clicking the New button,
点击这个按钮
you can type in the name of the repository
给你想要上传的项目
that you'd like to create related to your project,
起一个名字
a short description, and if you have a paid account,
一个简单的简介 如果你是付费会员
you can choose whether you'd like that to be a private or public repository.
你还可以把项目设成“只对你可见”
Once you create the repository,
一旦你创建完这个代码仓库
you'll see this page with directions about
你会在这里看到一些提示
how you can get started with this on your local machine.
告诉你如何把代码上传到 GitHub
By copying this portion right here or clicking the README portion,
点击这里 你也可以手动为你的仓库
you can create your own repository.
添加 ReadMe 文件
I'm going to copy this URL,
我现在将拷贝这个链接
and then by going to my local machine,
然后回到我自己的电脑上
I'm on my desktop and by using git clone and typing the URL,
打开我的命令行 然后输入 git clone 以及刚刚拷贝的链接
I can clone this repository to my local.
我就可以把 GitHub 上的代码仓库克隆到我自己的电脑上了
It gives me a warning that says there's nothing in this which is fine,
这有一个提示说 我们的项目里还没有任何的内容
because if you're just getting started,
刚开始没有什么关系
you can move all your project files into this repository later.
之后你可以把项目文件慢慢地上传进去
Now, the Project-1 here is something that we can move into,
这里有一个叫 Project-1 的文件夹  我们可以进去
which you can see is empty.
你看到它现在是空的
Let's say we add a few files.
现在让我们加入一些文件
So now, we have these couple of files,
现在 我们有几个文件
and we might want to add those to our project.
我们想把它们加入到我们的项目中
First, we'll use the git add command,
首先 我们使用 git add 命令
and we can use a star if we just want to add everything that's in the repository.
如果我们想把所有修改的内容都批量加入到项目中 我们可以用一个星
Otherwise, we can individually list them.
否则我们也可以单独地加入它们
If you check the status,
让我来检查一下状态
you'll see that they aren't yet committed.
你可以看到我们还没有上传修改
We can commit them in this way,
我们可以这么来提交
and then add this -m to also create our message at the same time.
然后加入这个 -m 为我们的提交加入说明
Now, you can see that we've committed them.
现在你可以看到我们已经提交了它们
However, they don't exist on this remote repository.
但是 GitHub 远程仓库里还没有它们
You can make sure to add them to this repository
通过 git push 这个命令可以将内容
that anyone can access by using the git push command.
上传到远程仓库里
Once you've done that, you should end up with a page similar to this
如果上传成功那你就能看到类似这样的页面
where you'll see each of the files that you've pushed located up here.
在这里你可以看到你提交的文件
It may ask you for your username and
你可能需要输入你的 GitHub 用户名
password related to GitHub to get this final process done.
和密码 进行上传